Claire left in a delivery truck?
How could you let her leave?
Ms. Cha told the chairman
we couldn't open the vault,
so she could replace
Ms. Claire's project with hers.
You just won't stop, will you?
If you don't want my dad
to switch the project,
just bring Claire here now.
Can we open the door now?
You knew all along that
my aunt is my weakness.
All I know is
I have to keep my promise to you.
Did you think Ms. Cha would let you live
if she found out
you weren't the real Claire?
About what you asked.
I remember
the pilot drank coffee before boarding.
Are you sure I'm nothing more
than a dog, Ms. Cha?
You're well aware
that I'm more than that.
Cha.
If you're upset,
you can stay at my place.
It's okay.
I just don't wanna go home
and get scolded by my dad.
What about Tunlathon?
What about him?
Aren't you gonna do anything?
Just go home, Chris. Can I be alone?
Go.
Go!
Cha!
What did you do to her?
I didn't do anything.
I bumped into her.
She lost her balance, so I caught her.
How dare he lay a hand on me?
Next time, even if I fall
and break my limbs, it's my business.
Don't ever touch me again.
If you don't know your place,
I'll have Dad fire you. Got it?
Yes, ma'am.
You can go now.
He really didn't do anything?
Why do you ask?
Well,
you looked so furious at him.
I thought
he must've done something to you.
Geez, Mom. It's nothing.
I already can't stand him.
Don't overthink it. I'm just tired.
I have to go. I'll call you later.
What is she doing out here at this hour?
What are you doing?
Making you pay
for what you did to me earlier.
Is that all you've got?
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
I understand why you had to do it.
Where is she?
Cha?
Are you in there?
Mom. What are you doing here?
I followed you.
What are you doing in here?
Just walking and thinking about work.
I couldn't sleep.
What about you?
I came to see what you were
sneaking around doing.
Sneaking around?
I was just walking
and thinking about work.
What?
You expect me to stay cooped up in my room
and play the maid's daughter?
Cha, don't you pick a fight.
I'm not. It's true.
Anything else?
I'm going to bed. I'm sleepy.
DELETE
BANGKOK - LADPRAO
MARCH 7TH
New customer. Please take their order.
Yes, sir.
What can I get for you?
What do you recommend?
I'll go get you a menu.
No need. Just tell me.
But the menu has pictures of the dishes.
In case you'd like to see them.
What the hell!
I just said I didn't want to look.
Can't you understand?
Is something wrong, ma'am?
- Are you the manager?
- Yes.
Did you train your staff
to argue with the customers?
I'm very sorry.
But don't worry. I'll take your order.
Go on. Head to the kitchen.
Please have a seat, ma'am.
Excuse me, ma'am. Is something wrong?
Nothing. I'm just going
to warn everyone online
so they don't have
the same awful experience.
Hold on, ma'am. Please calm down.
I'm truly sorry.
If there's anything I can do
to make this right, just let me know.
Are you sure?
You get it, right?
I do.
Thank you.
Chan.
Hey, stop, Chan.
Are you mad at me?
I just don't want you working as a waiter.
You don't want me working at all.
You show up and cause trouble,
preventing me from working there.
I don't want you working.
Chan.
What if something happens to me
while you're at work?
Aren't you worried about me?
You've been fine for a long time.
What if it happens again? I don't care.
I don't want you working.
Your job is to take care of me.
Answer me one question.
Do you love me?
What does "Mm" mean?
Do you love me or not?
Are you going to say it?
If you don't,
I'll hug and kiss you right here.
No, Claire. There are people around.
I don't care.
You know that.
So, do you love me?
Of course I do.
- Claire.
- You're the best.
- People will see.
- So what, Chan?
Let me take a picture as proof.
So whenever you see it,
you'll remember telling me you love me.
Smile.
Come on, smile.
That's enough. It's embarrassing.
What's with you?
This angle's better.
This side looks nicer.
-People are staring.
- See? Much better.
Smile.
DELETE
Hey. I remember now, about what you asked.
What is it?
I remember the pilot drank coffee
before boarding.
He drank coffee?
The pilot really was drugged.
THE BLOOD TEST CONFIRMED
THE PILOT WAS DRUGGED
So... what... does it mean?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
It's late. Aren't you coming to bed?
I'm not sleepy. You go ahead.
Why is that?
Do you really think
Claire kept that secret in the vault?
Is that why you wanted
to see it for yourself?
You should stop thinking about this.
The proof Claire claimed
she had doesn't exist.
Do you know why?
Because I never did that.
If I was going to cheat on you,
I would've done it back
when you were sick.
Why would I think that?
This move might be better.
Mr. Thiwa.
Were you even listening to me?
Did you know?
They say playing Go trains you
to read people's minds.
Because every move
reveals what the player wants.
Just like a lot of people.
Everything they do is
for the one thing they want.
Can you stop focusing on
this stupid game and hear me out?
Why would anyone do anything
if they get nothing in return?
I know. I understand. I heard you say
you never cheated on me. That you love me.
Then let me ask you this.
If I wasn't leaving anything
to you or your daughter,
would you still love me?
Let's talk about this later.
I'm going upstairs.
Don't be long.
Please look after him.
I hope you didn't stay up for us.
No.
I had a lot on my mind today,
so I decided to play Go to clear my head.
Do you like playing Go?
You know I always play it
whenever I need to think.
Play a game with me.
I don't know how.
Uh, I mean I don't remember
how to play this game.
Come on, play a game with me.
- Uh...
- Sir,
I don't think she...
You should try it.
You used to beat me at this.
Even if you've forgotten,
I'm sure some of it is still with you.
Come on, just one game.
What would you do?
How about this?
I would do this.
If we don't separate black and white,
and put them all together,
then we've claimed the whole board, right?
Oh, you're right.
Now that's thinking outside the box.
Why didn't I think of that?
Come on, Grandpa.
The game's over. It's time for bed.
You've had a long day.
Fine, I'll go to bed.
I look forward
to seeing what you two came up with
for the 60th anniversary event.
Okay.
I didn't expect you to mess up his board.
I don't think he expected it either.
Wanna know the truth?
What truth?
I didn't want him
doing anything stressful.
Today was stressful enough.
Then he played a stressful game.
I was worried it would affect his heart.
So I just messed up the board. How's that?
Thank you.
Huh? Wait...
Am I hearing things?
Did you just thank me?
What's that for, huh?
Well...
For looking out for him,
even though
he's not your real grandfather.
I don't know.
Maybe I've grown attached to him.
We're helping each other.
You take care of my aunt,
and I take care of him.
You know, you and him
are actually a lot alike.
How?
You're both awful at smiling.
See? There it is.
Oh, you're acting cool. Give me a smile.
Smile.
Stop acting cool.
I need to take this call.
Can you go to your room on your own?
Wait.
About what I asked you
regarding the pilot today...
don't tell anyone.
Who would I tell?
You don't let me talk to anyone.
Just making sure you know.
I know now.
I'm going.
Hello?
Were you able to recover
the data from Claire's phone?
Yes.
Did I forget to close the door?
What?
- Ms. Claire!
- He killed me.
- He killed me! He killed me!
- I said he killed me.
- Ms. Claire.
- Can you hear me?
He killed me. He killed me. He killed me.
I said he killed me.
Can you hear me?
Mr. Chan, it's all your fault.
I was finally starting to forget.
Now I'm dreaming about her.
Ms. Claire, you said...
you'd have nothing to live for
once your grandfather was gone.
- But what about Mr. Chan, your fiancé?
- What about him?
People who are engaged
are supposed to love each other.
Aren't you worried...
he would be sad
if something happened to you?
Sad?
I think he'd be the happiest one
if I died.
Does that mean...
he wanted Ms. Claire dead?
Cha.
How are you feeling, dear?
Are you excited
for your first day at work?
Thank you for trusting me
with a job at TGL.
Listen to you.
Of course your dad trusts you.
But that's because he sees your talent.
Otherwise, why would he let you
work at the company he loves?
Right, honey?
Don't let your mom and me down.
I won't.
Why didn't you run it by me, Grandpa?
Come on.
It's just hiring a new employee.
Why would he need permission?
Besides...
I've never seen...
a chairman ask the vice chairman
for permission to hire someone.
That would be absolutely ridiculous.
Really?
Well, I've never seen a maid
give unsolicited advice like you do.
Grandpa.
If you want her to work,
send her somewhere else.
We have plenty of companies. Why TGL?
I don't want to work
with a maid's daughter.
Why not? Afraid she'll outshine you?
Cha. Don't, dear.
What did you just say?
I'm telling the truth, Mom.
This maid's daughter
may end up contributing
more to the company than someone...
who does nothing but cause trouble...
just because
she's the chairman's granddaughter.
- Watch your mouth.
- Cha!
- Claire!
- Big mouth, aren't you?
- Claire, stop!
- Claire!
- Ms. Claire!
- Mr. Thiwa!
- Honey?
- Please stop, Ms. Claire. Please stop.
You dare stop me?
Please don't upset the chairman.
Please stop, Claire.
You want me to stop?
Fine.
- Claire!
- Who do you think you are?
A guard dog doesn't get to bark
at its master. Got it?
Yes.
Look at me.
Claire!
Claire, stop!
Stop it, Claire! I said stop right now!
- Ms. Cha?
- I brought your medicine.
You should go.
If Ms. Claire sees you,
you'll be in trouble again.
What? You think I can't handle myself?
I'd like to see
what else that bitch can do.
Besides...
you're her bodyguard.
You helped me back there.
She'll think you're taking my side.
Why did you do it?
Maybe because...
I can't stand...
seeing her hurt you.
Cha. Come here.
What now, Mom?
I think we should
get rid of Claire quickly.
I don't care how--
Kill her, cripple her, make her disappear.
What's going on? What are you up to?
Last night, Mr. Thiwa implied
he was leaving everything to Claire.
- Huh?
- I don't know...
if he was testing me.
But I'm not taking even a 1% chance.
You're well aware
if Claire becomes the chairman,
she won't keep us around.
Where's Mr. Chan today?
He's not here to boss me around.
He had an urgent matter.
Did you need to talk to him?
No.
I actually wanted to talk to you.
About what?
Well,
he asked me yesterday
if the helicopter pilot
ate or drank anything before takeoff.
I was wondering why he wanted to know.
Why didn't you just ask him?
Well, he was just curious,
so I didn't want to pry.
Hey. Do you know anything
about Ms. Claire and Mr. Chan?
I was wondering if they had a fight,
or if there was something more serious.
Are you saying...
you think Mr. Chan
was involved in the crash?
Whoa, no. That's not what I mean at all.
I don't know.
He didn't seem that upset,
so I started wondering.
Anyway, forget it. Ignore me.
He's always been like that.
Who knows?
He might be the one hurting the most.
He's unavailable today.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Hold on.
There's somewhere I'd like to go.
Could you take me there?
Why this temple?
I used to come here with my aunt.
It's so peaceful here.
Actually, I came to
make merit for Ms. Claire.
I dreamed about her last night.
Besides, ever since the crash...
and I've had to become her.
I have no idea how she feels.
So I wanted to let her know.
Then go ahead. I'll wait in the van.
Write the name of the deceased
and bring it to me.
Who was the deceased to you?
A friend, sir.
KHAEDARUN KANCHATHARA
- Wan?
- You?
KHAEDARUN KANCHATHARA
Thank you.
And what about you? Why are you here?
To make merit for my late friend.
Perfect.
She's making merit
for her late friend as well.
Please write your late friend's name
on the paper.
Then bring it to me.
Here.
JINLA PHIANDAIDEE
Next, prepare to make the offering, okay?
KHAEDARUN KANCHATHARA
JINLA PHIANDAIDEE
Ms. Wan.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
Neither did I.
Did you make merit for Ms. Jinla?
The last time we met, I could see
how devastated you were over her.
So I figured you came here for her.
Ms. Wan.
If you have a moment, I...
Could you please leave me alone?
I got fired.
Happy now?
What?
Don't pretend to be nice.
I know what you're like.
You were mad about
what I did to you that day.
So you pressured my company
to fire me, didn't you?
What else do you want to do to me?
Hurt me?
Slap me?
Go ahead.
I'm standing right here.
She thinks I killed Claire?
I don't know what Ms. Claire told her.
After you asked about the pilot,
she started getting suspicious.
I think it's time you tell her the truth.
Maybe it's better this way.
So she'll stay alert.
You should too.
From what I found out, that pilot
was filling in for our regular pilot.
What are you saying?
Hey, Chan. I have to go. Talk later.
How was it?
Did it make you feel better?
Did you guys pressure
The Contenic to fire Wan?
What?
I just ran into Wan.
She came to make merit for me.
Wan...
Oh, you mean Wanwali, your friend?
Yes.
Her company fired her.
Was that Mr. Chan's doing?
I don't think he'd do that.
I think her company fired her
as punishment
and to take responsibility.
I know what she did was extreme.
But she did it
because she was upset about me.
Ms. Wan came all that way to attack you.
Don't forget, you're a celebrity
and the vice chairman of TGL.
Did you expect her company to do nothing?
Let's just go.
I don't think Chan would like me
bringing you here.
Here, Mr. Chan.
I'm sorry we couldn't repair it.
But it's not a problem.
I was able to recover the data
for the new phone.
I saved all of Ms. Claire's data on it.
And I cloned the SIM card for you.
You can just pop it into the new phone.
If that's all, I'll take my leave.
SATURDAY 9 MARCH
MOBILE
SLIDE TO ANSWER
What if we hired Wan?
What do you mean?
She lost her job because of me,
so I want to help her out.
I don't think it will work.
I know you want to help your friend.
But Chan wouldn't allow it.
This is about your safety
and your secrets.
But just this once.
Would he really say no?
I'm Ms. Claire, Vice Chairman of TGL.
On the outside, yes.
But no matter what,
you're not the real Ms. Claire.
Take me to the office.
I've just realized something.
No matter how hard I try,
I can never become the real Ms. Claire.
So why must I be exactly like her?
Yes, Ms. Claire?
Call a meeting with every department
involved in the 60th anniversary event.
Yes, Ms. Claire.
TYCOON WITH A HEART OF GOLD,
DONATES 120 MILLION FOR MEDICAL EQUIPMENT,
A MODERN-DAY SAINT
From now on,
I'm gonna be Claire in my own way.
You called a team meeting?
Have you lost your mind?
Ms. Claire wants you to work for us.
I bet Ms. Claire's faking amnesia.
Or she wouldn't go on Wonder's show.
By now everyone knows
Claire's out of the hospital.
They'll look for another chance to strike.
Please welcome Ms. Cha
with a round of applause!
- Whoa, sir!
- Who sent you?
- No one, sir! Ow!
Would you like to kneel at my feet
and apologize to me?
MS. KHAEDARUN OPENS UP
AFTER SURVIVING A NEAR-DEATH EXPERIENCE